Prosper Lolo

Freelancer

PROFILE

I am a young man who is motivated to make a success out of himself. I take pride in whatever I engage myself in so that it is done to the best of my abilities. I am task and goal orientated, work well under pressure, and don't mind going the extra mile to achieve the desired results. I would like to gain experience and hopefully become the best at what I do.

EXPERIENCE

Freelancer

Self-Employed

- Develop applications and websites.
- Design websites giving a good user interface and user experience

2022

· Graphic Designer

Developer

Cobweb Developers 2021 - present

• Design, develop and deliver websites and applications to clients according to specifications

Soft Skills

• Managed the database of the company.

Freelancer

Self-Employed 2020 - 2021

• Worked in a team as a frontend developer

SKILLS

Hard Skills

Communication skills Html/CSS

Punctuality JavaScript

Problem-solving React

Critical thinking NodeJS

Teamwork PHP

UI/UX Design

Python

MySQL

Adobe

C++



CONTACTS

(+27) 659 444 353

loloprosper17@gmail.com

Website: www.prosperlolo.com

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/prosperlolo

Address: 76 Albert Street, Marshalltown

Johannesburg, 2111

EDUCATION

2021-Present

BSc in Computer Science and Informatics University of Johannesburg

2014 - 2018

National Senior Certificate

Queens High School

LANGUAGES

English •••• French ••••

Swahili ••••

References: To be provided if needed